const AI_quiz2 = [
	{
        	"question": "It is the complete history of everything that the agent has ever perceived.",
        	"options": [
            	"Percept Sequence",
            	"Concept Sequence",
            	"Performance Measure",
            	"Agent function"
        	],
        	"correctAnswer": "Percept Sequence"
    	},
     	{
        	"question": "An objective function that determines how the agent does successfully.",
        	"options": [
            	"Percept Sequence",
            	"Agent Program",
            	"Performance Measure",
            	"Agent function"
        	],
        	"correctAnswer": "Performance Measure"
    	},
     	{
        	"question": "A type of agent that are working in the environment that may not be the real world.",
        	"options": [
            	"Omniscient Agent",
            	"Learning Agent",
            	"Intelligent Agent",
            	"Software Agent"
        	],
        	"correctAnswer": "Software Agent"
    	},
    	{
        	"question": "Rational Agents are the problem, task environments are the solution.",
        	"options": [
            	"True",
            	"False",
            	"Maybe",
            	"None of the above"
        	],
        	"correctAnswer": "False"
    	},
    	{
        	"question": "An environment that is not changing over time but the agent's performance score does.",
        	"options": [
            	"Static",
            	"Semidynamic",
            	"Dynamic",
            	"Episodic"
        	],
        	"correctAnswer": "Semidynamic"
    	},
        {
    "question": "Who created the chatbot Dr. Sbaitso for MS-DOS that is a fully voice operated chat program and would converse with the user as if it was a psychologist?",
            "options": [
                "MIT",
                "Microsoft",
                "Google",
                "Creative Labs"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Creative Labs"
        },
        {
    "question": "Who created the chatbot A.L.I.C.E. (Artificial Linguistic Internet Computer Entity) that is a universal language processing chatbot that uses heuristic pattern matching to carry conversations?",
            "options": [
                "Alan Loebner",
                "Kenneth Colby",
                "Richard Wallace",
                "Eugune Goostman"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Richard Wallace"
        },
        {
    "question": "What is the 2001 chatbot that was in many ways a precursor of Siri?",
            "options": [
                "ELIZA",
                "Google Bard",
                "SmarterChild",
                "Chat-GPT3"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "SmarterChild"
        },
        {
    "question": "What is the chatbot developed by Apple for iOS in 2010 that is an intelligent personal assistant and learning navigator that uses a natural language UI?",
            "options": [
                "Alan Turing",
                "Google Duplex",
                "Alexa",
                "Siri"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Siri"
        },
    {
    "question": "What is the chatbot launched at Google Inch in 2012 which answers questions, performs actions through requests made to a set of web services and makes recommendations?",
            "options": [
                "Google Now/Google Assistant",
                "Google Duplex/Google Voice",
                "Google Alexa/Amazon Alexa",
                "”Simsimi"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Google Now/Google Assistant"
        },
        {
    "question": "What is the chatbot first demonstrated at Microsoft’s Build 2014 developer conference and became directly integrated into both Windows phone devices and Windows 10 PCs?",
            "options": [
                "Alexa",
                "Cortana",
                "Microsoft Edge",
                "Bing"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Cortana"
        },
        {
    "question": "What is the intelligent personal assistant developed by Amazon and introduced in 2014?",
            "options": [
                "Alan",
                "Amazon",
                "Alexa",
                "America"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Alexa"
        },
        {
    "question": "IBM’S _________ beats the world champion Garry Kasparov in the game of chess.",
            "options": [
                "Deep Blue",
                "Depth Blue",
                "Dr. Sbaitso",
                "Stephen Hawking"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Deep Blue"
        },
    {
    "question": "A robot car named ______, built by Stanford’s racing team, won the DARPA Grand Challenge",
            "options": [
                "Kachiga",
                "Lightning McQueen",
                "Nemo",
                "Stanley"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Stanley"
        },
    {
    "question": "IBM’s question answering system, _____ , defeated the two greatest Jeopardy champions, Brad Rutter and Ken Jennings.",
            "options": [
                "Watson",
                "Southstar",
                "Mercury",
                "Watsons"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Watson"
        },
        {
        "question": "What are the types of Artificial Intelligence?",
        "options": [
            "Artificial Small Intelligence", "Artificial Commander Intelligence, Artificial Ultimate Intelligence",
            "Artificial Closed Intelligence", "Artificial Generalistic Intelligence, Artificial Superior Intelligence",
            "Artificial Narrow Intelligence", "Artificial General Intelligence, Artificial Super Intelligence" ,
            "Artificial Manmade Intelligence", "Artificial Organic Intelligence, Artificial Supreme Intelligence"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Artificial Narrow Intelligence, Artificial General Intelligence, Artificial Super Intelligence" 
    }


]
